yesterdaystractors.com 2001-12-11

# Yesterday's Tractors - Privacy Statement

**Marketplace**  
Tractor Manuals  
Parts & Supplies  
Classified Ads  
Photo Ads  
YT Store  
Videos  

**Community**  
Forums  
Tractor Town  
Live Chat  
Hauling Schedule  
Auctions & Shows  
Contacts  
Tractor Cafe

**Research & Info**  
Site Search  
The Daily Dose  
Article Archives  
Photo Gallery  

**Specs & Values**  
Sale Reports  
List Prices  
Production Nbrs  
Tune-Up Specs  
Tune-Up Guide  
More...

**Fun & Games**  

**Just for Kids**  
Tractor Pictures  
Tractor Stories  
Coloring Book  
Interactive Story

**Miscellaneous**  
Submit an Article!  
Advertising Info  
Feedback Form  
Links

[ ](http://www.ytmag.com/cgi-bin/redirect.cgi?AD=YTgiveaway) |  **Yesterday's Tractors Privacy Policy**

Yesterday's Tractors is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of site visitor information. 

Site Visitor Information

During the process of delivering information to you, Yesterday's Tractors does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Yesterday's Tractors does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Yesterday's Tractors is used for the purpose of monitoring site statistics. 

If you would like additional information about the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by Yesterday's Tractors please [contact us](mailto:privacy@yesterdaystractors.net). 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information when filling out our [Feedback Form](http://www.ytmag.com/rdrform.htm) or participating in other areas of our site. This is voluntary on your part. Yesterday's Tractors does not sell or redistribute any of this information. 

Third Party Privacy Policies

Yesterday's Tractors works with third party advertisers that serve advertisements to this site. To find out more about how these advertisers manage the privacy of internet users please read the following: 

  * This site uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data typically through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to http://www.engage.com/privacy. 
  * Doubleclick, Inc.: <http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm>

**[[ Home ]](http://www.ytmag.com/index.htm)**
